# Rampi Federico Daniel Full Stack Developer

federampi@gmail.com Cel.: +54 9 3772 459589 Paso de los Libres, Corrientes - Argentina.

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a **Full Stack Web Developer** and computer technician, I have experience working with JavaScript, React, Redux, Express.js, among others. I consider myself a proactive person, with logical thinking, I do well working in a team because I believe that cooperation is the best method to solve problems and to meet the objectives.

I am a curious person, who is always reading about new technologies and different methods or ways to improve my code

My goals are, to put into practice the skills I have developed, to continue learning new technologies and best practices, also to join a team and collaborate with my experience. I am open to all opportunities that allow me to grow either as **Front end**, **Back end** or **Full stack**.

### **SKILLS:**

HTML

Tailwind CSS

Node.js

Postman

CSS

React

Express.js

Sequelize

JavaScript

Redux

Git y Github

PostgreSQL

#### **PROJECTS**

### Full Stack Web Developer - Pi Pokemon

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop a pokemon App that includes: pokemon search, pokemon detail display, filtering, sorting, paging and creation.
- For the development I used React, Redux, pure CSS for the Front end and Node.js, Express for the Back end.
  Database in PostgreSQL and Sequelize. Repository | Deploy

#### Full Stack Web Developer - Henry Bank

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop an App-mobile that includes: searches, filtering, sorting, user registration, login with authentication, administrator panel, user profile, news, payment gateway and transfers, fixed term, buying and selling cryptocurrencies, mailing system, etc.
- For the development we used React Navite, CSS, Redux, Figma for the **Front end** and Node.js with Express for the **Back end**. Database in PostgresSQL and Sequelize. JWT was used for authentication, Nodemailer for mailing and Stripe for card payments.
- In this project I worked on the **Back end** side, we worked using the SCRUM methodology where we used Trello to write down the tasks to be done.

Frontend repository | Backend repository | Demo

## LANGUAGES

• Spanish: Native

• Ingles: B1 Intermediate EF SET Certificate

## **PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION**

### **Full stack Developer**

Bootcamp Soy Henry | Feb. 2022 – Ag. 2022 |

• 700 hours of theoretical and practical courses.

## IT infrastructure technician

Instituto Superior De Formación Docente Profesor Agustín Gómez | Feb 2012 - Dic 2013

• Career focused on preventive and corrective maintenance of computers, both hardware and software, also focused on the installation and maintenance of computer networks.

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

## **Technical Support**

Jan 2014 - Jul 2022

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes, Argentina

Repair of desktop computers, notebook, etc. both hardware and software,

installation of programs, like operating systems, office automation, etc.

Also back up files and also file recovery, installation of network cable (utp), installation of cameras, etc.

## IT Technical Support | Intern at Paso de los Libres Customs Office

Ag. 2013 - Nov. 2013

Paso de los Libres, Corrientes, Argentina

Maintenance and installation of wired and wireless networks, repair of computer equipment, both software and hardware, repair of printers, etc.